学习口音有两种方式：一次到位，或者一步一步来。
There are two ways to pick up the accent, all at once or step by step. There's the
一种是“现在就做”的人，另一种是喜欢慢慢改变、认为太快发生的事
do it now people and the people who like to change slowly thinking that there's no
人们不太相信来得太快的东西是真的。
validity to things that happen quickly to them. People don't think it's real if it's
如果来得太快，人们就不觉得真实；但这正是 Nike 的口号：just do it。
fast but that's the Nike slogan, just do it. You know you can and even if it's
速度可能比你想象的还快，但这种方法依然有效。关键都是行为模仿。你
faster than you expect it's still valid. It's all about behavior modeling. You
你不必先相信它，只需要去做。一次到位：just do it。听
don't have to believe it, you just have to do it. All at once. Just do it. Listen to
听声音和节奏，抓住几个核心元素，然后开始说。一步一步来。
the sounds and rhythms, capture some essential elements, and go. Step by step.
逐项应用每个技巧，发展你的音质、发音、
Apply each technique one by one to develop your voice quality, pronunciation,
在你掌握了每一个元素之后
intonation, phrasing, and linking. After you've mastered each of these elements,
如何把它们整合进说话里。哪种方法最适合你？我们会
work on integrating them into speech. Which method will work best for you? We'll
首先尝试一次性方法，看看我们能否用这个快捷方式启动你。
try the all-at-once way first to see if we can jump-start you with this shortcut.
这与其说是美式口音，不如说是你是否真正去做。
This isn't so much about the American accent as much as it's about you doing
纯粹模仿。不要思考，不要过度分析。
pure mimicry. Don't think. Don't overanalyze. Just imitate exactly what you
你听到的每个方面：音质、发音、节奏、断句和词语
hear in every aspect. Voice quality, pronunciation, rhythm, phrasing, and word
流动。
flow.